Next story.
Breaking news on the Okutama
serial kidnapping and killing case.
Police report
numerous eyewitness sightings.
However, no concrete evidence
has surfaced so far.
We had a special fortune reading performed
by Shingetsu Nathan, the practitioner
of the Dragon-Surge Style divination.
He has given his predictions
on the culprit.
He predicts the killer
is a thin, handsome male in his late 30s
with a hunched back. What do you think?
Mr. Nathan has
successfully predicted events in the past.
They're here.
Coming.
Do we have a guest?
Miss Emma, please clear the table.
Sure.
Thank you.
-For you.
-Thank you very much.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
This is Diane. The architect
who designed this guest house.
-It's wonderful to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
And… the salesperson.
I'm Mathew. Shota Mathew.
Did you forget my name?
I've been with Diane's architectural
studio since her father was in charge.
They will lead the reconstruction
of the main house,
so you'll see them around.
Understood.
This is Emma. She's boarding
with me for the time being for reasons.
-I'm Sho Emma. It's a pleasure.
-Likewise.
-Good to meet you.
-Good to meet you too.
-Thank you.
How are your parents, Miss Chloe?
I called to tell them about the fire.
They gave me an earful,
saying I shouldn't be living alone,
so I hung up right away.
Your parents live elsewhere?
Miss Chloe's parents
live on an upper floor
of a city high-rise.
A newly built apartment in the city center
is more comfortable than
an old house where cold drafts seep in.
A salesperson that leaks personal info
must be detrimental to your business.
Yes. I'll terminate him.
What? Oh, sorry.
I thought there'd be no harm
since you two seem close.
Switching gears.
I saw some signage by the entrance.
Did you start a fortune-telling business?
Yes. I'm only open once a week,
on Sundays.
Remember when you gave me a reading,
and your predictions came true?
Yes. When you were deciding
to go independent.
-Yes.
-How nice.
Miss Chloe, won't you read my fortune too?
A salesperson who's overly friendly
with his clients…
I'll terminate him.
Where do you draw the line then?
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
How considerate. Thank you.
Back to business.
Will this be a total remodeling?
Well…
The main house
didn't completely burn down.
I see.
As an architect,
I'd like to make use of the main house's
eclectic revivalism features.
Let's preserve those features
the best we can, and…
I believe your father
is the original architect.
Yes. This is the first house
he designed upon returning to Japan.
This provincial-style house inspired
by French and Belgian architecture…
I lost them there.
Diane is rather particular
about her tastes, you see.
She drives a compact car by a French
manufacturer. It's a convertible.
Fancy, I know.
I hear when she separated
from her ex-husband--
Mathew?
Was that taboo?
Hold on, I was being mindful
to not discuss her personal life…
First of all, don't talk
about somebody else's private life.
Sorry. I was just trying
to make conversation…
Speaking of someone who's particular,
you're very fashion-conscious.
Am I?
But don't you want to wear clothes
that put a pep in your step?
I wear something that makes me happy
when I'm meeting people.
But when I'm at home,
I want to be relaxed,
so I tend to wear silk.
That was silk you wore…
You're picky when it comes
to fashion too, Emma.
You wear neutrals for your basic fit,
then wear bright pajamas.
Indeed.
I cycle through ten simple items
in black, white, gray, or beige.
That way, I can blend in anywhere.
So you're like Steve Jobs.
I don't think hers is quite like
Steve Jobs' stoicism.
And she doesn't wear just one outfit.
Since I've been on a job hunt recently,
I'm trying to wear neutrals
that won't offend anyone.
And now, I'm boarding rent-free.
I don't have the luxury
of wearing the clothes I like.
That's why, at least to sleep,
I wear cheery pink polka dots.
I was merely stating facts.
I never said
you shouldn't wear flashy clothes.
They say what you wear to sleep
reveals your actual taste in fashion.
Speaking of,
I wear a silk pajama to sleep--
-Sorry, shall we continue?
-Wait, I--
-Hey, I was--
-Now, please take a look.
-Let me see…
-Listen…
I wear a silk pajama.
This is the image of the finished house.
Today, I wore this pink necktie, and…
What about…
-Chloe.
-Emma.
-Chloe et Emma.
CHRONICLE CARD FORTUNE-TELLING
SORT
RITSUKO BABA
SUGINAMI - APRIL 11TH, 2006
Ritsuko Baba.
Yes.
So, what brings you in today?
I think my boyfriend, who attends
the same university as me, is cheating.
You think he's two-timing?
Well, yes. For now.
But I think he wants to get back together.
Get back together?
Yes.
He might be cheating on me with his ex.
Maybe he got tired of me
because I'm gloomy and don't stand out.
Although, he's the one who insisted
I tone down my looks.
What do you mean?
He doesn't like it when I stand out.
We started dating in high school.
At first, he complimented
everything about me.
But recently, he's either critical of
or disappointed in me.
My parents
always told me to be careful
because men go for girls like me.
Maybe that's why my guard was
always up around men.
He was the only one
who broke down my walls.
I don't want to lose him.
So you want to know
what the future holds for you two?
Yes.
Understood.
-Thank you. You're good to go.
-Okay.
Hello.
-Hello.
-Do you have a reservation?
Yes. I'm Masahiko Sorita.
Come have a seat.
Please write down your name,
address and birthday.
'Kay.
MASAHIKO SORITA
SHINJUKU - JUNE 28TH, 2002
Masahiko Sorita. Are you employed?
Yes.
So…
I like someone,
but I can't get her to trust me.
I don't know how to move forward.
Okay.
She works at a café near my work.
I try to approach her,
but she brushes me off.
Do you make it sound like a joke?
Not at all.
She must know how serious I am.
Well, I'm signed with a modeling agency.
I'm a model.
This girl I'm interested in is…
Well, she's not conventionally
beautiful or attractive.
That must be why she doesn't believe me.
As in, she doesn't think
she measures up to you?
Probably.
Well, I'm not good with the popular type.
I find them intimidating,
so I understand where she's coming from.
But I feel at ease
when I'm around girls like her.
I don't have to pretend I'm someone else.
I want her to know the real me,
not just my looks, and then trust me.
What if you told her that, word for word?
I mean… I already have.
I see.
Then you want to know
how you can earn her trust.
I will also read
what the future holds for you two.
Please.
First a pretty girl, then a handsome guy.
Who would've known
your business would be such a hit?
Maybe your business is a hot topic
in the Beautifuls' social circle.
What kind of social circle is that?
I guess… being attractive doesn't
stop you from having issues.
Everyone's got issues.
But…
their cards for the near future
were the same.
That took me by surprise.
Which card was it?
Thursday, reversed.
Card of Greed.
When this card is in reverse
when reading the future,
it usually indicates
tumultuous relationships.
Tumultuous?
TRADITIONAL CAFÉ PARIS
You can be attractive and still
have rough patches in relationships.
What's the matter, Emma?
You havin' romantic troubles?
Want us retirees to lend an ear?
We're here for ya.
I was making a general statement.
Know what?
Attractive people tend to have
more issues in relationships.
They get hit on more, you see.
True. Now that you mention it, yes.
That's right.
Just like us.
-Of course.
-Right?
Back in our prime,
we broke a lot of girls' hearts.
Because we wore tacky outfits to dates!
Remember?
You had a killer pick-up line.
-Oh, that?
-Tell 'er.
Go out with me,
and I promise a lifetime of happiness…
-For myself.
This one was funnier.
C'mon, don't be harsh.
She liked this one more.
-Thanks for the food.
-Till next time.
Thank you for your patronage.
Thank you.
-Phew, it's hot!
-Sure is hot out.
Your glasses hide it,
but you're one of the Beautifuls,
just like Chloe.
Beautifuls?
Chloe took care of me
when I got caught between two girls.
In a way, she saved me.
Really?
During my first year at a company,
two female coworkers
started some huge drama fighting over me.
It got so bad, I had to resign.
Oh, dear.
After that, I worked part-time
in the kitchen of a diner.
But a similar thing happened.
A server and a kitchen worker
fought over me in front of the customers.
Good grief. You sure are popular.
What's this? Why're you out here, Emi?
The kitchen's slow.
I figured I'll help out.
You sure that's the only reason?
What're you insinuating?
Nothing. Just thought you were trying
to show off to a special someone.
Pipe down, you two.
Mana, here's the parfait.
I already went shopping
with Simon, you know.
Shopping?
You mean your breaks overlapped
so you took a quick shopping trip.
Did I nail it?
Sorry to drag you into this, Simon.
Never mind me,
but there are customers around.
Hear that?
You've put Simon in an awkward position.
Simon is mine.
I apologize for the trouble earlier.
Sorry to bother you.
Even though this place is part of a chain,
you guys serve the best parfaits,
and that's why I come.
And the customer from that day
was Chloe.
Right. Even though it was just a diner,
she noticed the care I poured
into making parfaits.
It made me happy.
My shift was wrapping up,
so I went after her and thanked her.
We were talking when
my parfait-making hobby got brought up.
I told her it was difficult
to create an original parfait
at a diner chain.
That's when…
That's when?
She asked me to tag along.
She took me to a certain place.
Where are we?
Your dream of making parfaits…
Ready to make it come true?
TRADITIONAL CAFÉ PARIS
"Your dream of making parfaits…"
It's got a nice ring to it.
She let me use the kitchen here.
That's when I made
my first off-menu parfait.
My first attempt at
the chocolate banana crunch parfait.
So there's history to that parfait.
In the end, I left the diner.
I said I wanted to open a parfait shop
for grown-ups as I worked here.
But the prior owner suddenly retired
due to his old age.
That's how I ended up taking over.
So that's the story.
Yes.
But the biggest relief
is that Chloe doesn't try to date me,
and she put me in a place
where I'm free from unwanted advances.
I don't have to worry
about getting hit on.
There's safety that comes with it.
Also, I get to make parfaits every week.
That's the story behind
the weekly parfait night.
That's right.
I don't mean to complain
after all she's done for me,
but isn't she a bit too generous?
But she hates it when people
come begging for her help.
She can be quite cold to them.
Really?
She can't help but lend a hand
to people who've been wronged
but are trying to better their situation.
She's good-natured.
So if I had said "please help me"
rather than "I hate to impose,"
then maybe she wouldn't have
let me use her restroom.
I've gotta be careful.
She's letting me stay
out of sheer generosity.
She might decide to kick me out
on a whim one day.
Guess nothing's changed
since I lived with my ex.
Speaking of, you said your relationship
wasn't on equal ground.
When there's a power imbalance,
I have to be careful I don't come across
as annoying or unlikable.
Still, you have to be assertive to get by.
When a tiny woman like me is quiet,
I get bulldozed over.
I see.
Be bold and carefully read people so that
I don't cross the line and be hated.
That's my pro tip for life.
That's quite challenging.
-Welcome in.
HARUKA MIMASAKA
MITAKA - MAY 3RD, 2005
Haruka Mimasaka.
Are you a student?
Yes. I attend a university.
What brings you in today?
I'm getting approached by two men at once:
my ex and a customer at work.
Are you seeking guidance
on which man to date?
Neither of them feel quite right.
Meaning?
My ex is my junior from middle school.
Though he's younger,
he can be quite persistent.
I gave in, and we dated for a while.
Over time, he grew careless with me.
Although he's not that attractive himself,
he'd call me ugly and fat.
Like, I'm well aware.
He didn't need to say those things.
Even after we split,
I still felt hurt by his words.
I see.
As for the other guy…
I work at a café. The second floor
is a modeling agency.
We have a lot of models that stop by.
For some reason,
one of the models
has taken an interest in me.
But my ex says
there's no way a hot guy would like me.
That he must have some ulterior motives.
Do you still talk to your ex?
He… started messaging me a while ago.
He irritates me,
so I've been ignoring him.
Then…
Do you want to know whether
this model is really in love with you?
Well…
How about this?
Shall we ask the cards
what's making you feel unsettled?
Yes, please.
Understood.
Oh,
mon…
Dieu
!
The first card.
It represents your current situation.
Friday, reversed. Card of Order.
Things have been strange for you lately.
Embarrassment. Turn of events.
Do you feel uneasy
about the turn of events so far
and out of balance because of it?
Yes.
Something about this model
feels off to me.
He says he feels comfortable
around me because I'm not beautiful.
It feels like he's hung up on appearance.
I see.
The second card.
It represents something from the past
that continues to affect you.
Saturday, reversed. Card of Stagnation.
You feel stagnant because of
changes in how someone treats you.
Something impedes your growth.
The third card. The inner self.
September, upright.
Card of Reflection.
Face…
You've been reflecting on your appearance.
But it's upright,
meaning it's a change for the better.
People may call me fat or ugly,
but I don't let that stop me
from enjoying my life.
People who judge others like that
only do so
because they want to feel superior.
The fourth card. The outer world.
Monday, reversed. Card of Hesitation.
A love triangle gone awry.
Also, I sense a dark secret.
The final card.
It represents an event in the near future.
What is it?
Thursday, reversed.
Card of Greed.
You will
be in a direct confrontation.
You might get caught in a fray.
What?
Your lucky color is black.
Black?
Those earrings are black.
Is it a slice of bread?
Actually,
my ex made this for me when we went
to an accessory-making workshop on a date.
He made me burnt toast earrings.
Crazy, huh? He made me burnt toast.
I like that cheesy sense of humor.
I thought about throwing them away
when we broke up,
but they go with a lot of outfits,
and I just really like them.
Those earrings didn't wrong you.
Let go of relationships,
but not their keepsakes.
This is it. I've pieced it together.
Card of Greed completes the picture.
What picture?
The pretty girl, the model guy,
today's client
and the shitty ex
just might form a love square.
A "love square"? And who's the shitty ex?
I'll explain.
Ritsuko Baba, the first client,
is dating the shitty, abusive boyfriend.
He used to date
Haruka Mimasaka, today's client.
Masahiko Sorita, the model, likes her.
See how everything lines up nicely?
Can such a small community actually exist?
Remember, I recently opened
this small fortune-telling business.
I don't have a website,
social media page, or run newsletters.
Not may people should know about me.
At first, these things spread
through word of mouth.
It's highly likely
they're connected somehow.
I guess.
To top it off, their last cards
for their future were Greed, reversed.
This cannot be a coincidence.
Everyone got the card
of relationship woes, huh?
The shitty ex's identity was the last
piece I needed to complete the puzzle.
And I found him
through my brilliant social media search.
You shouldn't meddle
in your clients' personal lives.
But I can't leave a mystery unresolved.
You're just rubbernecking at this point.
Look.
Ken Tsukumo. First-year
economics major at Sawa University.
He's the shitty ex.
How'd you even find him?
I found a mutual friend
of the pretty girl and the shitty ex
who can't help but shares his entire life
online for all to see.
THIS ACCOUNT IS PRIVATE
Good golly.
Ristuko Baba
is the prettiest girl in her grade.
When she started dating Tsukumo,
people at their school were bewildered.
It caused quite a commotion.
I've heard of pretty girls
who date losers.
No man is brave enough to ask out
a girl who's out of his league,
except for an oblivious rando
who rushes in and dates her disastrously.
I was also able to identify
Masahiko Sorita's modeling agency.
Haruka Mimasaka's café is
directly below this agency's office.
Tsukumo and Mimasaka were in the same
swim team at the same middle school.
See how all the dots connect?
Also, this must be the accessory workshop
they visited together.
SAIBU WORKSHOP
CREATE A ONE-OF-A-KIND TREASURE
Congratulation, Chloe.
You're a fully-fledged online stalker.
Let me summarize.
Although he has a girlfriend, the shitty
abusive boyfriend hits on his ex.
His girlfriend catches on
that he's fooling around.
The hot model
is into average-looking girls.
The ex-girlfriend is wary
of both her ex and the model.
Baba should break up
with a loser like him.
That's what's scary about abusers.
They manipulate their victims
by tearing down their confidence.
So, what's your plan?
Who am I, a complete stranger,
to meddle in their love affairs?
You're merely sating your curiosity.
Thank goodness.
Although…
"Although"?
I wonder what chaos would ensue
should these four be put in the same room?
Chloe?
I'll set up bait.
They might remember my face,
so I'll have you do the leg work, Emma.
Don't drag me into it.
Please, Steve Jobs.
Now is the time
to use your talent for blending in.
Are you mocking me? Are you?
Please, Steve!
Are you ready?
No!
The first step…
First, I make contact with Tsukumo
at his college campus
by dropping the burnt-toast earring
and making it look like an accident.
He then picks it up.
Excuse me.
That's mine.
Here you go.
Where did you get that earring?
Isn't it cute?
It's in the shape of burnt toast.
I saw a café employee with it.
I thought it was cute, so I made one too.
The employee said hers are also handmade.
She said she cherishes them.
I tell him I saw a café employee
with an identical set.
By the way, what's the name of the café?
Café Isnikyac.
A modeling agency
set up office right above them,
so they get a lot of attractive guys
who swing by.
Well, not like that's any of your concern.
Bye then.
I feed him information
about Mimasaka's job.
Mentioning the attractive customers
is part of my plan to make him jealous.
While I'm on the move,
I want you to chat with Mimasaka
about egg sandwiches.
Nudge her so that she becomes
interested in Traditional Café Paris.
FOLLOW
Apparently, Mimasaka loves egg sandwiches.
Excuse me.
It should go according to plan.
Thank you.
Wow, this is delicious.
Do you like egg sandwiches?
They're my favorites too.
Are there any restaurants
or cafés around here
that are known for their egg sandwiches?
To name a few must-visit spots,
there are Café Trumbo and Jelly…
But they're always packed.
I know, right?
That's why I go
to Traditional Café Paris in Mitaka.
They're usually pretty empty
in the evening.
Their egg sandwiches are exquisite.
I see. Traditional Café…
Paris.
-Paris.
-Yup.
Welcome in.
I finally found you.
Why'd you ignore my messages?
Why're you here?
Can't you see I'm working?
I'll wait 'til you're done.
Don't. You're bothering me.
I'll stop by every day.
Will you listen to me then?
Anyway, I'll see you after work.
Go wait elsewhere.
How about Traditional Café Paris
by Mitaka station?
Why Mitaka?
Why not? I'll head over at five,
when I get off.
-Promise?
-Promise.
TRADITIONAL CAFÉ PARIS
One egg sandwich and tea, please.
A spaghetti Napolitan for me.
Understood.
One egg sandwich and one Napolitan.
Yes.
Chloe? What's with the outfit?
I must see this mission through.
Once Mimasaka and Tsukumo arrive,
I'll stage a photo with them
"accidentally" in the background.
I'll then post it on Paris's
social media account.
No need to nudge Baba,
she'll come on her own.
POST
She's a café lover who already
follows Paris's account.
TRADITIONAL CAFÉ PARIS
Thank you for waiting. Enjoy.
Let me snap some photos.
Phew, your Napolitan's steamy.
Looks delish.
I'll post a pic on my account.
Don't copy me.
You're the one trying to get likes
using my food.
Mimasaka, the egg sandwich lover,
has a habit of uploading
pictures of egg sandwiches
along with hashtags
and information about the café.
I POST INFO ON CAFÉS
WITH TASTY EGG SANDWICHES!
Sorita, the hot model,
follows Mimasaka's account.
He should catch on that she's here.
It's out of this world!
You sure eat like you love food.
You want to say that's why I'm fat, huh?
No. Just thought I like
how happy you look.
You can't sweet-talk me
into getting back with you.
Isn't there a hot model who's into you?
You already know
he's not a good match for you, right?
-None of your business.
-Well, you should follow your gut.
I've dated a pretty girl before,
but everyone looks at you like you've got
no right to be with an attractive person.
Before long, you start to take
everything they say the wrong way.
Life was simple
when I was with you, Haruka.
Didn't you feel the same?
You treated me carelessly toward the end.
I'm really sorry.
I was immature.
Recently, all I can think about
is the good times we shared.
Remember the accessory-making workshop
we went to together?
I made weird earrings,
and you couldn't stop laughing.
What was it? What did I make again?
Right. Burnt toast!
I loved how you wore them all the time.
Did you throw them away?
Look how strong he comes on.
So that's how abuse starts.
This place is empty.
I didn't mean to get it…
Welcome in. For one?
You never took interest in things I wear.
-Say what?
-Interest.
Tsukumo.
Ritsuko? Why're you here?
-Hey…
-You know her, Ken?
I'm his girlfriend.
How'd you know I'd be here?
That's you in the background, right?
That's how you found out where I am?
You creep me out.
I want a Napolitan too.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
One Napolitan, please.
Just a moment, Miss.
Welcome in.
For one?
-Everyone's here.
-Sit wherever you'd like.
Ritsuko, don't stalk me anymore.
It really gets on my nerves.
Why are you going behind my back
to meet up with your ex?
You used to date him, right?
Yes.
I can meet with whomever I want.
See how controlling you are?
This is why no one else but me
would ever date you, you get that?
Hey, Ken.
I might have dated him,
but I have no intention
of getting back with him.
You can relax.
And I don't plan on ever
talking to him again.
Wait, what?
Seriously?
Look what you've done.
You're ruining my friendships.
How will you make up for it?
Do you realize what you've done?
Why do you do this to me?
That's too far.
It's for her own good.
Otherwise, she'd never stop.
She might be pretty, but she's immature.
Hey, you--
I'm saying this for your own good.
If you stalk me again,
I'm cutting ties with you.
Then you'll be left all alone.
You understand that?
I know I've got no right to say this,
but why are you dating scum like him?
He's hitting on his ex while he's dating
you. Don't you see how shitty that is?
I bet you're saying that to break us up.
Do you want to get back with him?
Come on. He's not worth fighting over.
Wow, you're so rude.
Everything you've said so far is abusive.
You're tearing down her confidence
so you can feel superior to her.
Sorry to keep you waiting. Your Napoli--
I know.
You're jealous because she's pretty.
Say what?
Are you satisfied that an ugly girl
like you got to tell off a beautiful girl?
I know you are.
You're the worst.
-Here's the Napolitan--
-Hey!
Will you stop criticizing Mimasaka?
You're the one fixated on appearance.
Masahiko?
I heard Mimasaka got
in a spat with a customer.
I got worried and came looking for you.
The café owner told me everything.
I used your hashtags
as a clue to come here.
You creep.
You're a stalker just like Ritsuko.
You're the one who tracked down
her workplace and barged in uninvited.
Here's your Napolitan.
Let's go, Mimasaka.
He's projecting his own insecurities about
his appearance on you and his girlfriend.
Are you unaware of how condescending
you sound right now?
Just what I'd expect
from someone as attractive as you.
Listen. I don't think
I'm better looking than anyone.
Don't worry about appearances.
I chose you. Won't you trust me?
It doesn't sit right with me.
Ken tells me not to step out of line
because I'm ugly.
Masahiko says he doesn't care if I'm ugly.
Either way, you're both
fixated on appearances.
To me, both of you sound condescending.
If that's how I came across,
then I apologize.
Besides, I never
used the word "ugly." I just--
You said popular girls are intimidating.
That's why you prefer me.
Because I'm not the popular type,
meaning, you like unattractive girls.
You'd rather date a girl
who's a downgrade.
It sure is more comfortable that way.
That's not what I meant.
People who think they are beautiful
tend to be haughty.
They don't even realize
they're looking down on others.
Aren't you describing yourself?
That was astute, Ritsuko.
What? Who are you again?
At least, I've never made fun
of the people around me.
I know I'm no one special.
Here's a thought.
Maybe you're used to being degraded
by the people in your life.
Exactly. And sorry to say this,
but objectively speaking,
he treats you like trash.
Butt out of our business.
She's the one who needs me.
Seriously, why does it have to be him?
She's right. You're bound to find
a better man in a heartbeat.
You hear that? What're you going to do?
We all have different reasons,
but all three of us think
you'd be better off without me.
Why don't you break up with me
and doll up like this model?
Like he said,
you'll get swarmed by trashy men.
You're really pretty, after all.
You're the worst.
You're the one who's trash.
He got that right.
There you go. Silent treatment again?
Want me to decide for you?
I won't break up.
I'm never breaking up with you.
What? Why?
He's my first boyfriend,
and he took my virginity.
I even enrolled in a university
below my grades to be with him.
If I break up with him now,
then my life from 17 to 19,
the most wonderful time of youth,
would be wasted.
Come on. That's like losing out on a bet
and digging a deeper hole
to recover from it.
The faster you break up with
this shitty guy, the better off you'll be.
What's wrong with you,
calling me a losing bet and shit?
He's not shit.
I didn't waste my life on a shitty guy.
I love him, regardless
of his personality and appearance.
What's wrong with that?
Did I hurt someone?
He's got the worst personality around,
and his features are average at best.
So what?
For me, there's no one else but him,
and for him, there's no one else but me.
I'm the only one he can treat like this.
We're a good match. We suit each other.
Isn't that enough?
She really didn't hold back.
You good?
That was a bit much.
What?
Me? It's my fault?
I professed my love for him.
Sorry about the Napolitan.
I'm sure the pasta's soggy
and your arm is tired.
Right.
Sorry for the wait.
Here's your Napolitan.
Digging in.
In this world,
there are as many types of hell
as there are people.
I thought you were going
to solve everyone's problems
like they do in cartoons and dramas.
I had nothing to say.
Thinking I could swoop in
and save the day…
Really, I was misguided.
Thanks for waiting.
Nice.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
This week, I made
a grown-up karinto parfait.
The bottom layer is
hoji tea and lemon jelly.
It's topped with crushed
brown-sugar karinto and yogurt cream,
as well as blueberries and raspberries.
At the center is
bamboo charcoal ice cream.
At the top are
salt-and-black-pepper skinny karinto
and a bamboo charcoal tuile.
A Japanese parfait for grown-ups indeed.
-Time to dig in.
-Thank you for the parfait.
The black pepper and salt
bring out the karinto's sweet flavor.
They're in perfect harmony.
A yummy parfait is a great way to forget
the hell we witnessed.
My own lack of insight, shortcomings,
the negative emotions of others…
This is a ritual to purge them all.
To tell you the truth,
karinto parfait is how I got started.
What?
When I was in elementary school,
someone stole my recorder.
Don't worry, we found the thief.
My teacher said, "She stole it because
she likes you. Can't you let it go?"
No way.
It didn't sit right with me.
Why do I have to be the bigger person?
I went home feeling depressed.
My parents gave me karinto to cheer me up.
I don't dislike karinto per se,
but back then, I was furious
it had to be karinto.
It was the last straw,
and I started bawling.
You must have wanted pudding
or another soft and sweet treat
after such a rough day.
But then, I found a tub of yogurt
in the fridge,
so I made a karinto yogurt parfait.
All I did was pour yogurt
over some karinto.
I bet it felt fancy.
I felt a bit better after I finished it.
I see.
Little Simon had to pull himself up by his
bootstraps and find his own happiness.
We all dream that someone can
come into our lives and make us happy.
Expect it, even.
But life is full of regrets
and what-could-have-beens.
In the end, you're
the only person in the world
who can provide the happiness you seek.
Life is about coming to that realization.
Maybe that's the thing
that separates us from them.
But you know…
it takes privilege to realize that.
Come again?
We have to be somewhat comfortable
before we can come to that realization.
Money, beauty, talent…
I hope we can live in a world
where people who lack all these things
can still enjoy
delicious parfaits like this.
You have to get on your feet first.
I know.
I hope you can afford Simon's parfait
with your own money soon.
Yes.
I will work hard so that I can
open my own parfait shop someday.
You can bet on it.
I'll pour you some tea.
Thank you.
Yogurt and brown sugar karinto…
It's a match made in heaven.